{
    "id": "f5d6ad3503c84d02b3debb7116ecd91e",
    "title": "Reported Speech",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Rahul said that he ............................... fiction.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "likes",
                "liked",
                "liking"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "4b423b79ca3443d7aa58caec265363ac"
        },
        {
            "question": "The girl said that she ....................................... writing a letter.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "was",
                "had"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8492b6a93cb34034b9423484c9fa945c"
        },
        {
            "question": "The boy ...................................... that he was waiting for her.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "said",
                "told",
                "asked"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "5809ba54f13a450eb37e32dae580be1f"
        },
        {
            "question": "The masons ......................................... that they had finished the job.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "said",
                "told",
                "asked"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "7e55a78a15a740889aa7d9626bc289c3"
        },
        {
            "question": "The boy said that he ...................................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "had selected",
                "had been selected",
                "selected"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7a1dd1961e6e4a1cba7200503dc6a30a"
        },
        {
            "question": "The teacher asked the girl if she .................................... her homework.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has done",
                "had done",
                "did"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6776d8449a18467fa39487c4e723bca7"
        },
        {
            "question": "The teacher encouraged the boy ............................................. hard.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to work",
                "working"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "00f8e54fdc8c410bb07d8297a7aee553"
        },
        {
            "question": "The man said that he .......................................... his bag.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "lost",
                "has lost",
                "had lost"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "e956890ea91345ad806f31156c5fc2a0"
        },
        {
            "question": "The traveler asked where the nearest inn .......................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "was"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "369b4abbaaad4139a8966c06fc40e1c6"
        },
        {
            "question": "I asked him ............................................ he would help me.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "if",
                "what"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "9f102f129cf24ff99455be73122cc65d"
        }
    ]
}